Register of the Vladimir J. Bastunov Collection, 1897-1917.
Hoover Institution Archives
Vladimir J. Bastunov Collection,
1897-1917
75102
Bastunov, Vladimir J., collector
4 manuscript boxes (1.7 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Imperial orders, military orders, personnel rosters, and casualty reports, relating to the operations of the Russian Imperial Army and its personnel.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1975.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Russia. Armiia.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Russia.; Russia.
Container List
- Casualties, August-December 1914 (Box 1.)
- General list of commanding and other responsible persons in the government of the Russian Empire for the year 1911
- Imperial order on military-education institutions
  - August 6, 1909
  - August 6, 1910
  - August 6, 1911
  - August 6, 1913
  - July 12, 1914
- Imperial orders, excerpts, 1909-1910
- Imperial orders on awards of the Order of St. George for the Russo-Japanese War, 1904-1905
- Imperial orders on military-educational institutions, 1907, 1912 (Box 2.)
- Kazan' Military District, XVIth Army Corps, 1910-1917, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc.
- Kiev Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc.
  - Headquarters and IXth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - Xth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XIth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XIIth Army Corps, 1908-1915
  - XXIst Army Corps, 1910-1917
- Moscow Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc. (Box 3.)
  - Grenadier Corps, 1910-1916
  - Vth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XIIIth Army Corps, 1910-1916
  - XVIIth Army Corps, 1905-1917
- Nikolaevsk Imperial Military Academy, list of graduates, 1902-1911
- Odessa Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc.
  - VIIth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - VIIIth Army Corps, 1905-1917
- St. Petersburg Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc.
  - Ist Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XVIIIth Army Corps, 1910-1917
- Vilnius Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc. (Box 4.)
  - IIIrd Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - IVth Army Corps, 1910-1916
  - XXth Army Corps, 1897-1916
- Warsaw Military District, orders, personnel rosters, casualty reports, etc.
  - VIth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XIVth Army Corps and 45th Infantry Division, 1910-1917
  - XVth Army Corps, 1910-1917
  - XIXth Army Corps, 1910-1917